https://www.hwdressage.com/privacy/

Thank you for visiting HWDressage.comThis Privacy Policy  and Terms of Use Policy sets forth the online information practices of Holmberg & Wadeborn Dressage, a partnership  (“HWD”), including:TERMS OF USENever begin riding or any physical activity without first checking with your doctor or physician. Equestrian activities are a rigorous sport, with the potential risk of injuries.  The creators, producers, participants & distributors or sponsors of this website shall not be held liable in any way what so ever for any and all advice given on this site.  Viewers are strongly urged to seek out certified professionals during all such activities.  Viewers who engage in these equine activities, do so at their own risk.PRIVACYOur pledge to have reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USEHWD collects two kinds of information from you: personally-identifiable information that you choose to provide to us and non personally-identifiable information, such as your IP address. Personally-Identifiable Information e-MailThe only personally-identifiable information that we collect is what you voluntarily submit to us. For example, if you e-mail questions or requests for information about HWD,  its products and its services, we may request your name, mailing address, telephone number and/or e-mail address in order to respond to your inquiries.If you submit a resume or application for employment with HWD via e-mail, you will be required to include personally-identifiable information so that HWD can adequately review your application and contact you. HWD may collect and store the information you choose to provide us in order to send you information about HWD from time to time.Products and Services Offered By HWD or by Third-Party VendorsThe HWD web site offers software downloads which may require the user to enter personally-identifiable information.This information will be used to process your request. MMD also may offer links to third party sites, which may offer products or services for sale. Please note that MMD does not usually process orders or ship merchandise and that HWD does not dictate or supervise the information collection and use policies of any third party vendors. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other web sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit for more information on how your information may be collected and used.Non Personally-Identifiable InformationIP Addresses An IP Address is a number used by computers on a network to identify your computer so that data can be transmitted to you.  We collect IP Address information in order to administer our web site and to gather broad demographic information.Cookies Cookies are pieces of data that a web site sends to a user’s computer while the user is viewing the site. Cookies identify your web browser and store information about your visits, but do not reveal any personally-identifiable information about you. We may use cookies to understand what parts of our site users are visiting the most and to help us improve our site.Information Sharing We may share personally-identifiable and/or non personally-identifiable information with select third parties, including our agents, affiliates, partners and sponsors. Also, we may disclose personally-identifiable information when required to do so under law or in cooperation with a legal request in connection with any law enforcement investigation or other public safety matter.CHOICE HWD provides you with the following choices regarding the use of your information:You may choose to not provide us with any contact information. However, if you do so, your ability to navigate this site may be impaired. If you would like to change or modify information you have previously provided us, please contact us via our Contact form in in the”About” section.If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of our web site, please contact us via our Contact form in the ”About” sectionNOTIFICATION OF CHANGESIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.SECURITYWe make every effort to have reasonable security procedures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. If you have any questions about the security of our web site or about this privacy policy, please contact us via our Contact form.Updated Policies:  September 3, 2017
Thank you for visiting HWDressage.comThis Privacy Policy  and Terms of Use Policy sets forth the online information practices of Holmberg & Wadeborn Dressage, a partnership  (“HWD”), including:TERMS OF USENever begin riding or any physical activity without first checking with your doctor or physician. Equestrian activities are a rigorous sport, with the potential risk of injuries.  The creators, producers, participants & distributors or sponsors of this website shall not be held liable in any way what so ever for any and all advice given on this site.  Viewers are strongly urged to seek out certified professionals during all such activities.  Viewers who engage in these equine activities, do so at their own risk.PRIVACYOur pledge to have reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USEHWD collects two kinds of information from you: personally-identifiable information that you choose to provide to us and non personally-identifiable information, such as your IP address. Personally-Identifiable Information e-MailThe only personally-identifiable information that we collect is what you voluntarily submit to us. For example, if you e-mail questions or requests for information about HWD,  its products and its services, we may request your name, mailing address, telephone number and/or e-mail address in order to respond to your inquiries.If you submit a resume or application for employment with HWD via e-mail, you will be required to include personally-identifiable information so that HWD can adequately review your application and contact you. HWD may collect and store the information you choose to provide us in order to send you information about HWD from time to time.Products and Services Offered By HWD or by Third-Party VendorsThe HWD web site offers software downloads which may require the user to enter personally-identifiable information.This information will be used to process your request. MMD also may offer links to third party sites, which may offer products or services for sale. Please note that MMD does not usually process orders or ship merchandise and that HWD does not dictate or supervise the information collection and use policies of any third party vendors. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other web sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit for more information on how your information may be collected and used.Non Personally-Identifiable InformationIP Addresses An IP Address is a number used by computers on a network to identify your computer so that data can be transmitted to you.  We collect IP Address information in order to administer our web site and to gather broad demographic information.Cookies Cookies are pieces of data that a web site sends to a user’s computer while the user is viewing the site. Cookies identify your web browser and store information about your visits, but do not reveal any personally-identifiable information about you. We may use cookies to understand what parts of our site users are visiting the most and to help us improve our site.Information Sharing We may share personally-identifiable and/or non personally-identifiable information with select third parties, including our agents, affiliates, partners and sponsors. Also, we may disclose personally-identifiable information when required to do so under law or in cooperation with a legal request in connection with any law enforcement investigation or other public safety matter.CHOICE HWD provides you with the following choices regarding the use of your information:You may choose to not provide us with any contact information. However, if you do so, your ability to navigate this site may be impaired. If you would like to change or modify information you have previously provided us, please contact us via our Contact form in in the”About” section.If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of our web site, please contact us via our Contact form in the ”About” sectionNOTIFICATION OF CHANGESIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.SECURITYWe make every effort to have reasonable security procedures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. If you have any questions about the security of our web site or about this privacy policy, please contact us via our Contact form.Updated Policies:  September 3, 2017
